<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>nate601&#39;s blag</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on nate601&#39;s blag</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Post Mortem: Rapere Librum</title>
      <link>/2019/06/22/post-mortem-rapere-librum/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/06/22/post-mortem-rapere-librum/</guid>
      <description>Mobile development is something that I have attempted once or twice, but I have yet to create anything tbut I have yet to create anything with which I was happy. Development for iOS devices requires a computer running MacOSX, which I have not had in the past. The only computer that I had access to for development could not be updated past OSX High Sierra due to its age, and OSX Mojave is required to install the lastest version of xcode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Terminal Workflow</title>
      <link>/2019/06/14/terminal-workflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jun 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/06/14/terminal-workflow/</guid>
      <description>Recently I have made several changes to my terminal workflow, and I feel that it would be useful to document them so that I may analyze any changes that occur in the future.
Windows Environment I perform most of my activities within a windows environment. I use Cmder as my terminal interface. I have several utilities placed within the Bin folder, allowing access to them without cluttering my PATH. I have the Git for Windows version which gives access to what is essentially the CoreUtils package.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Continuing Education</title>
      <link>/2019/05/25/continuing-education/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/05/25/continuing-education/</guid>
      <description>## Warning in library(package, lib.loc = lib.loc, character.only = TRUE, ## logical.return = TRUE, : there is no package called &amp;#39;plyr&amp;#39; The intent of this document is to provide myself with a way of tracking the status of my progress for me Continuing Education Units (CEs) for the rest of the month of May.
It is currently 2019/05/25. I must have 20 hours of CEs by the end of this month.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About Me</title>
      <link>/aboutme/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/aboutme/</guid>
      <description>Introduction Name: Nathan Button
Contact Information: LinkTree
Pronouns: He / Him
Age: 20
Drink/Smoke: No
Available times: Evening - Night
Profession: Pharmacy Technician / Student
 Sharables 1 Gaming Style - Strategy or 4x mainly, but I’ll play whatever my friends are playing
Recent Game(s) -
 Dwarf Fortress
 VALORANT
  Recent Anime(s) -
 Mob Psycho 100
 Kaguya-sama: Love Is War
  Recent Song(s) -</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Weekly Game Jam 93</title>
      <link>/2019/04/19/weekly-game-jam-93/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 19 Apr 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2019/04/19/weekly-game-jam-93/</guid>
      <description>Day 1: Day one of WGJ-93 is going fairly well. The theme selected was “fishing.” The game that I have decided to create is a simple non-tactics based game where the player controls a fish hook. This fish hook must dodge things such as jellyfish and driftwood, while still capturing fish. Fish capturing is handled by mousing over the fish for a certain amount of time. The amount of time is determined by the size of the fish (i.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>